Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Advance Convention Advisory, Jul 22 1980 (Box 48, Folder 126)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: RRC urges Governor to sign Toxic Substances Warning Bill, Jun 26 1980 (Box 48, Folder 127)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: State AFL-CIO opposes Court Employee Bill, Jun 10 1980 (Box 48, Folder 128)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Passage of Casino Gambling Legislation during the current session, Jun 11 1980 (Box 48, Folder 129)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett urges Senate to approve Meaney Convention Center Bill, Jun 10 1980 (Box 48, Folder 130)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement by RRC on Labor Disputes in Nursing Homes Assembly Labor Committee, Jun 5 1980 (Box 48, Folder 131)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement by RRC urging Amnesty for Transit workers from unreasonable Taylor Law penalties, Jun 4 1980 (Box 48, Folder 132)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett urges Amnesty for Transit workers, Jun 4 1980 (Box 48, Folder 133)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett urges Nursing Home investigations, May 22 1980 (Box 48, Folder 134)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: AFL-CIO to challenge Boiler Regulation Report in Court, May 14 1980 (Box 48, Folder 135)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement by RRC on Boiler Regulation Repeal, May 5 1980 (Box 48, Folder 136)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett attacks Assoc. Ind. over Boiler Regulation, May 5 1980 (Box 48, Folder 137)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement of RRC on NYC Transit strike, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 138)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: AFL-CIO position on the NYC Transit strike, Apr 5 1980 (Box 48, Folder 139)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett urges Governor to make money available for NYC transit settlement, Mar 28 1980 (Box 48, Folder 140)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Speakers scheduled for NYS AFL-CIO Legislature/COPE Conference agenda, Mar 20 1980 (Box 48, Folder 141)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: AFL-CIO withdraws from Labor Management Committee due to opposition to Boiler Rule, Mar 19 1980 (Box 48, Folder 142)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Press Advisory 1980 Leg. & COPE Conference at Kiamesha Lake, Mar 17 1980 (Box 48, Folder 143)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett urges naming of NYC Convention Center after George Meaney, Mar 12 1980 (Box 48, Folder 144)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Corbett outlines property Tax Program at Albany hearing, Mar 6 1980 (Box 48, Folder 145)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement by RRC on Legislative options for establishing a real property tax classification Subcommittee, Mar 6 1980 (Box 48, Folder 146)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: NYS AFL-CIO urges Gov. to ban J.P. Stavens Co. from bidding on state contracts, Feb 27 1980 (Box 48, Folder 147)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Telegram to NY Congressional Delegation to reject bill exempting work places from OSHA inspection, Feb 27 1980 (Box 48, Folder 148)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement on Toxic & Hazardous Substances & exposure to them in the workplace, Feb 21 1980 (Box 48, Folder 149)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Changes by Com. Ross to improve service to states unemployed workers praised by NYS AFL-CIO, Feb 12 1980 (Box 48, Folder 150)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Memorial Mass said for George Meaney at St. Patricks Cathedral, Jan 28 1980 (Box 48, Folder 151)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: Statement by RRC on death of Geoerge Meaney, Jan 11 1980 (Box 48, Folder 152)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: AFL-CIO Fact Sheets, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 153)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: AFL-CIO Statements, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 154)
  - Corbett & Cleary Speeches & Press Releases: AFL-CIO Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 155)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Executive Council Members, Jan 23 1987 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Save Our Industrial Base Rally, Jan 27 1987 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Council 82, AFSCME 3rd Annual Political Action Conference, Jan 27-28 1987 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Public Employees Federation Rally, Jan 29 1987 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Young Democrats of Brooklyn College, Feb 8 1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Workshop, Feb 10 1987 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Labor Religion Coalitions ACTWU, Feb 11 1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Cohoes Music Hall, Feb 11 1987 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Cornell University (Albany), Feb 12 1987 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, Feb 12 1987 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: WNY Dir. Legislative Cocktail Reception, Feb 20 1987 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Council 82, AFSCME Annual Political Action Committee, Feb 23 1987 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Schenectady Central Labor Council, Feb 25 1987 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Cohoes Music Hall Meeting, Feb 26 1987 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Economic Justice For All, Feb 26 1987 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT Executive Council Meeting, Feb 28 1987 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: United Way of NYS, Mar 3 1987 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Buffalo Nite, Mar 3 1987 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Central NY CLC & NYSUT, Mar 4 1987 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Union Counselor Training Course, Mar 5 1987 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUTs Board Directors, Mar 6-7 1987 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYUS Labor Committee Serv., Mar 10 1987 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS AFL-CIO Staff Meeting, Mar 11 1987 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT WNY Director Meeting, Mar 12 1987 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUTs Committee of 100, Mar 16-17 1987 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Virgil Hodges Dinner, Mar 18 1987 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Cornell Univ. Labor Advisory Comm., Mar 18 1987 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Illinois Federation of Teachers Convention, Mar 21 1987 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Public Employee Department, Mar 24 1987 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Upper Hudson Valley Labor Council, Mar 25 1987 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Ed. 1-4 Meeting, Mar 27 1987 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Bread & Roseo, Cornell University, Mar 29 1987 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS AFL-CIO Education Committee, Mar 30 1987 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Barboro 1987 Legislative Agenda for Labor, Mar 31 1987 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: New Hartford T.A. Meeting, Mar 31 1987 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Convention, Apr 2-4 1987 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFL-CIO Regional Conference, Apr 10-11 1987 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Cornell University Labor Adv. Committee Meeting, Apr 22 1987 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Buffalo CLC, Apr 24 1987 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Labor Religion Coalition, Apr 27 1987 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Ed. 1,2,3 & Vote/COPE Kickoff, Apr 28 1987 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: VFTs Spring Education Conference, May 9 1987 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSSILR Collective Bargaining, May 11 1987 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: ILR Advisory Council, May 13 1987 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: New Hartford Labor in the Schools, May 14 1987 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Committee of 100, May 18-19 1987 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Glenn Falls Union Counselors Graduation, May 26 1987 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: ACTWU Rally, May 27 1987 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Press Conference CWA-LCA Rm., May 27 1987 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Subcommittee on Aging, Mar 2 1984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Convention, Mar 15 1984 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS AFL-CIO Legislative Conference, Mar 27 1984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Vanderbilt University Conference, Mar 8-11 1984 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT, Williamsburg, VA Conference, Mar 12-15 1984 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Hennessey Meeting, NYC, Apr 26 1984 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: New Jersey Federation of Teachers, Apr 28 1984 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: E.D. # 1 & 2, May 7 1984 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: New York State Labor and Religion Coalition, May 8-9 1984 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS Council of Senior Citizens, May 14-16 1984 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: COPE / Cornell Political Action Institute Series, May 19 1984 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: ED 3 Meeting, May 21 1984 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Senior Staff Meeting NYS AFL-CIO, May 31 1984 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: COPE / Cornell Political Series, Jun 2 1984 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: National Commission on Secondary Vocational Education, Jun 5 1984 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Jun 8-9 1984 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Genesee Wyoming CLC, Jun 9 1984 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Lower Hudson COPE / Cornell Political Action Institute Series, Jun 16 1984 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Italian-American Labor Council, Jun 19 1984 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSSILR, Jun 20 1984 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: USWA, Jun 21 1984 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Union Label & Service Trade Department Convention, Jun 25-27 1984 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Bayberry Conference, Jul 6-8 1984 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT New Local Presidents Conference, Jul 9 1984 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Dan Sanders Meeting, NYSUT, Jul 11 1984 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Peter Peyser Meeting, Jun 27 1984 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: National Democratic Convention, Jul 16 1984 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: COPE / Legislative Candidate Endorsement Meeting, Jul 24 1984 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Stan Lundine Meeting, Jul 28 1984 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT, Aug 1 1984 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: 1984 Presidents Conference on Political Action, NYSUT, Aug 8-9 1984 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Jamestown CLC Annual Installation Dinner, Jan 9 1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSSILR Cornell Conference on Organizing in the 80s, Jan 12 1985 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Media Training Conference, Jan 15 1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Conformation Meeting on Pt 100 regs., Jan 15-16 1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Wisconsin AFT, Jan 16 1985 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Executive Committee Meeting NYS AFL-CIO, Jan 18 1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Executive Council Meeting NYS AFL-CIO, Jan 18 1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT Executive Council Meeting, Jan 25-27 1985 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT Domestic Democracy, Jan 28 1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Met Life Insurance Co. Education 85, Jan 29 1985 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Private Industry Council, Feb 6 1985 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Seminar for Reps on Job Training Partnership Act, Feb 6 1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT Executive Council Meeting, May 18-20 1985 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NY CLC Lincolns Birthday Dinner, Feb 9 1985 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Plight of the Collective Bargaining System, Barbaro Press Conference, Feb 12 1985 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, Feb 17-23 1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Feb 22-23 1985 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: PEC Annual Breakfast, Feb 26 1985 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT WNY Directors Meeting, Feb 27 1985 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFT Regional Conference, Mar 1-3 1985 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYC Office, Mar 5 1985 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Queensbury T.A., Mar 6 1985 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Community Services AFL-CIO, Mar 7 1985 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Luncheon for New Legislators TWU Local 100, Mar 8 1985 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS UT Spring Political Action Workshop Ed # 1-4, Mar 9 1985 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS AFL-CIO Labor Lobbyist Meeting, Mar 11 1985 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Shared Union Systems Inc., Mar 13 1985 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: AFL-CIO Annual Education Conference, Mar 19 1985 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Union Women, A Celebration with Family & Friends NYSUT, Mar 17 1985 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Press Conference on Legislation, Apr 1 1985 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYS Carpenters Labor Management Committees Annual Conference, Apr 1 1985 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Western NY Board of Directors NYSUT, Apr 10 1985 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NE AFL-CIO Council Meeting, Apr 16-17 1985 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Ed # 1-4, Apr 19 1985 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: 33rd Annual Institute of the NYC CLC Community Services Committee, CLC Rehab Council, Apr 20 1985 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: League for Industrial Democracy, Apr 24 1985 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Union Lawyers Conference, Apr 24 1985 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: Representative Assembly, Apr 25-28 1985 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Apr 25 1985 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Paul Coles Meetings: NYSUT Monroe Co. President Council, May 2 1985 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - AFL-CIO Press Clippings, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Americans for a Common Sense Budget, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Cleary Speeches, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Cleary Speeches, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - AFL Press, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Coors Boycott, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - CLC News/Notes, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - NYS Democratic Convention, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Police Press Releases, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Freedom House, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Griffin Media Group Correspondence, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Kleinberg Electric, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - 2nd Annual AFL-CIO Labor Recognition Dinner, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - AFL-CIO ORT Luncheon, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Police Correspondence, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Police Press Clippings, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Police Federation Speeches, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Police Federation Newspaper, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Testimony of Public Health Council, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Public Employees Federation, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Tobacco Institute Paper, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Tobacco Institute Special Project, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Tobacco Institute Press, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Tobacco Institute, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Tobacco Institute Phone Bank, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Tobacco Institute Correspondence, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Tobacco Institute Opposed Memorandums, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Travelers Media, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - UNITY, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Freedom of Information, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Harris Poll, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Intelligence Reports, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Labor Studies Project AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Labor & the Humanities, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Labor Curriculum (NYSUT), 1984 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Labor History ASSN, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Labor Column, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Labor Desk, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - NYSUT Math/Science, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - NEA Disaffiliation, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - NYEA, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - NYSUT Math/Science, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - LAFalce File, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Labor Letter, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Learning Styles, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - LPUT Workshop, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - LPUT Public Relations Committee, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - LPUT PR, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Leis Eulogy, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Math & Science Shortage, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Media File, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - NYSUT Internal Campaign, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - NYSUT Services, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - News Letters, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Labor Council, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - NYSUT Financial, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - NYSUT Labors Stake in International Affairs, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - NYSUT Tuition Tax Credit, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Organizing, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Our Town, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Shanker Column, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Student Rights & Responsibilities, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Work & Education, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Hennessey Meeting, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Frontlash, Jan-80 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Labor Council Endorsements, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Candidates Questionnaires, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - COPE Coordinators for Mondale, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - COPE District Coordinator, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Executive Council Motion: Mondale for President, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO Contributions to Candidates, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Candidate Congratulations, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Phone Banks for Mondale, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Phone Bank Volunteers, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - COPE Endorsements, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Phone Book Volunteers, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - National AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Voter Registration, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Keypunching Correspondence (Council Unions, etc.), 1984 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Updating, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Computer Bills, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - National Time Sharing & Data, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - AFL-CIO Reg. Meeting, Mar 23-24 1984 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Mondale-Ferraro, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - AFL-CIO Region 7 Director, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Apprenticeship Local 3 IBEW, 1986-1990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Associated Actors and Artists of America, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Abortion Issue, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Actors Equity Association, 1985; 1990 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Advocate Newsletter, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Tax Policy, 1991; 1993 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Ad Hoc Business and Labor Conference of NY State, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action Advisory Council, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Affordable Housing, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - African Famine Relief Drive NY State AFL-CIO, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - ALPA, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Allegany County Pension Fund, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Assembly Bill 838, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Alabama AFL-CIO, 1987; 1989 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Alaska State AFL-CIO, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Alliance for Consumer Rights, 1985-1994 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Allied Printing Trades Council, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1985-1991 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1986-1990 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1984-1985; 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - African American Labor Center, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - American Center for International Leadership, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - ACLU, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - American Express, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - AFGE, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - AFSCME, 1990-1995 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - AFSCME DC 82, 1985-1992 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1985-1991 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - American Catholic Lay Commission on Catholic Social Teaching, 1983-1985 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - American Flag, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - American Heart Association, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - American Income Life Insurance Companies, 1986-1990 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - American Jewish Heritage Committee, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - American Labor Museum, 1986-1990 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - American ORT Federation, 1985-1995 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - American Petroleum Institute, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - American Postal Workers APWU, 1990-1992 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - American Pre-paid Legal Services Institute, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross, 1987-1988 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - American Suffragists, undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - AT&T, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - American Tourism, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Amivest Corporation, 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Angel Guardian Home, 1984-1989 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Anti-Bugging Legislation, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Appalachian Council, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Appointments Governors Office, 1989-1991 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Apprenticeships NYC, 1984-1995 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Apprentice Training Program IBT Local 363, 1980-1984 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - AIDS, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Army War College, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Asbestos Control, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Arkansas State AFL-CIO, 1990-1995 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Asbestos Celotex, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors, 1984-1990 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Association of Benefit Administrators, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Association for a Better New York, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Associated General Contractors National Newsletter, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Association for Children with Retarded Development Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Ant-take Over Proposal, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Attorney General (Robert Adams), 1990-1992 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Auburn Correctional Federal Credit Union, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - August-AM Cal Advisors, Inc., 1987 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Bank Hapolim, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Bank for Socially Responsible Lending, 1986-1988 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Bankruptcy Code, 1984-1990 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Barbaro, Frank, 1984-1990 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Basic Trades of Rockland County, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Bastian, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Battery Park City, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Bayberry Land, 1984-1987 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Beach Systems Corporation, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Bellamy, Carol: Business Equity Program, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Bellmire, Merrick-United Secondary Teachers, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 17)